https://www.batteriesinc.net/privacy-policy1/

HomeAboutContactFAQShipping & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyShopTrack Your OrderMy AccountCheckoutPrivacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form. When ordering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name and email address. You may however, visit our site anonymously. What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we received from you)To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support your needs)To process transactions  (your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by you, the customer) Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.This policy was last modified on 03/24/2015 Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at:Batteries Inc. 36 Persimmon Street, Unit 301 Bluffton, SC 29910 customerservice@batteriesinc.net Bluffton, SC 29910 Phone: 843-706-9909 Email: customerservice@batteriesinc.netGet in touchProviding the best quality batteries, direct from DuracellBatteries Inc accepts the following forms of secure payment:
© Batteries Inc. 2019 - All Rights Reserved
